Oghenekaro Brume Israel

 Q Lagos, Nigeria
 ■ oghenekaroisrael089@gmail.com
 ● 08071380789

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/brume-israel-oghenekaro-581b44136/

https://github.com/oghenekaroisrael

Profile

A highly dynamic computer science student, skillful in implementing the design, architectural and algorithmic aspects of a system. A quick learner and thorough problem solver driven by building and launching new projects that solve problems and enhance capabilities with 5+ years experience in aiding companies tackle complex problems by identifying flaws within their systems and providing final solutions.

Education

08/2019 – present Ilishan-Remo, Nigeria **Bsc Computer Science,** Babcock University

2015 – 2017 Delta, Nigeria National Diploma, Delta State Polytechnic Otefe Ogbara

Professional Experience

07/2021 – present Sugar Hill, Georgia, USA

Intern FullStack Developer, IntellimedMedia

- I developed one Backend API with NodeJs and one Backend API with Django.
- I developed two frontend panels with React Js and One mobile app with React Native.

07/2021 – 12/2021 Lagos, Nigeria

Backend Developer Intern, *Lanepact*

• I learnt how to use NodeJs to build RESTful APIs

01/2021 – 06/2021 Lagos, Nigeria

Intern (Frontend And Backend), QuCoon Limited

- I Learnt how to use Kotlin to develop RESTful APIs.
- I Designed and developed multiple dynamic and responsive web pages using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- I consumed APIs using axis and fetch API.
- I was made a sub-team leader Due to my initiative, learning speed and adaptability to the workspace.
- I Worked closely with teammates including a supervisor to determine problems, testing strategies, and best practices.
- I Aided my teammates to complete their projects by determining problems, solving the problem

04/2018 – 08/2020 Warri, Delta, Nigeria

Software Developer, *Greenhouse Multimedia*

- I developed 2 working softwares for the company while upgrading 2 others.
- I trained 100+ users by clarifying role responsibilities and giving other key information to them.
- I spearheaded the process of information gathering from users
- I oversaw the management of Softwares and databases
- I gave advice of network and hardware purchases to aid Software and other facility activities.

Skills

Programming Language

Python, JavaScript, Kotlin, PHP

Database

MongoDB, MSSQL, MySQL

Project Management

Clickup, Wrike, Asana

06/2019 - 08/2019

Web Technologies

React Js, Django, Node Js, Express Js, Bootstrap,

Material UI

Version Control

GitHub, GitLab

Projects

04/2018 - 08/2020 MedAssistant (Hospital Management Software),

HTML, PHP, SQL, Jquery, Bootstrap, And Charts Js

0 0 0

A Hospital Management System with nine working modules (Doctor, Nurse, Laboratory, Pharmacy, Frontdesk, Account, Accident and Emergency, Operations,

and Admin)

Medpay Hospital accounting software, HTML, Bootstrap, PHP, Mysql, Javascript A Software Project

• I built an API to allow user login and accept payment for services rendered by the doctors, nurses and other departments of the hospital.

• I made a frontend to enable user login, accumulate patient bill from the different departments, manage stock and lots more.

• I made a frontend for the admins to manage and supervise operations.